Hello everyone, how are you all? I hope
you all are doing very well in your field. The
company's company results have been
declared recently. Today we will discuss
how the company's results were. Before
starting this, hello everyone, I am an MBA in
Finance. I am a certified research analyst
with 10 years of experience in the stock
market. If you have not subscribed to our channel,
please like, share,
subscribe, and hit the bell icon so that you can get
all our latest videos timely. Here are the
ICC Lord General Insurance's finance
results. All figures in last year's December
quarter, September quarter, last year's December quarter, nine months, this
year's end. Let's
talk about total income. 588,
283, 586,
54. There is an uptrend with respect to the last quarter.
Income in my sector has been
seen increasing year by year with respect to the last quarter. Talking about the database, 175, 43, 45, 94,
88, so there is an uptrend here as well.  Let's
talk about the name and expense in the total income
518 48 825 So with respect to the last quarter,
in expenses also
our expenses have been seen increasing year by year, let me do that
from the data base 152 443
13253 here also there are expenses, so
expenses have been seen increasing in my quarter and sector,
I am talking about the same, on the
9 data base also our expenses have been
seen increasing, let's talk about profit after tax
7248 69 395 43 46 there
is an up move with respect to the last quarter, an up
move has also been seen in the last quarter, so on
quarter by quarter and year by year basis
my results have been seen improving,
talking from the 91 data base 19970 1
3999 here also there is a good up move  There are
no details available on profit after tax, gross NPA and net NPA. Let's
talk about the stock. We have seen that
our quarterly results have been increasing. The
same trend has been seen here also with respect to
last year's
last quarter. The same is true for the
database. Here
too, a good up move has been seen. Here, the
database is true. Here are the total results. If you
want me to make a detailed video on this stock
based on fundamental analysis, please
comment in the comment box
section. This is from my side. Last but not the least.
Please like, share and subscribe. Hit
the bell icon and please share this video
with your friends, relatives and loved ones
so that they too learn something new through this video. Keep learning, keep earning. Thank you. Thank you everyone,
love you all.
[Music]